(Leonard:)That's it. It's
Sheldon's bedtime.
(Leonard:)He is in for the night.
(Penny:)Wow. I cannot believe we are
alone in our own apartment.
(Leonard:)It's weird.
(Leonard:)This must be how parents feel
(Leonard:)when their kid goes off
to college.
(Leonard:)Unless they feel sad--
then it's different.
(Penny:)So, what do you want to do?
(Leonard:)I know exactly what
we are gonna do.
(Penny:)Really? You're a genius,
(Penny:)and that's the first thing
you come up with?
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon's
not here,
(Leonard:)so we are going
to put on music
(Leonard:)and dance in
our underwear.
(Penny:)Ugh. Can we just have sex?
(Leonard:)Oh, don't worry.
(Leonard:)Once you see my sweet moves,
sex is inevitable.
♪ It was a teenage wedding
♪ And the old folks
wished them well ♪